Guide to the Development Alternatives, Inc. reports, 1977-1989
Development Alternatives, Inc. reports, 1977-1989
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Development Alternatives, Inc. Reports, 1977-1989
4463
Development Alternatives, Inc.
1 cubic ft.
Documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reports on projects in Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Thailand.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Reports on projects in Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Thailand.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Development Alternatives, Inc.
Subjects
Economic development projects--Asia, Southeastern.
Places:
Indonesia--Economic conditions.; Malaysia--Economic conditions.; Philippines--Economic conditions.; Thailand--Economic conditions.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- 1977, DAI; Project-Level Organizational Linkages and Integrated Area Development - The Case of Libmann/Cabusao IADP, Institutional/Agricultural Activities (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1977, Charles F. Sweet; The Bicol River Basin Development Project: Some Preliminary Observations (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Implementing Integrated Area Development in the Bicol: Recommendations and Observations Based on Libmann/Cabusao IAD, 1977; George H. Honadle (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Farmer Organization for Irrigation Water Management: Organization Design and Implementation in Bula and Libmanan, 1978; George Honadle (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Management Information Systems - Bicol River Development Program - Consultant Report, 1978; Dr. Alan Roth (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Political and Business Trends in Indonesia, 1980; Jerry M. Silverman (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Desiccated Coconut and Byproduct Production in Gorontalo District, North Sulawesi, Indonesia, 1981; DAI (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Village Fishpond Development Project in Thailand (#493-0303) 1979-1980, 1981; Joint Thai/American Evaluation Team (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Feasibility Study for P.T. Tudjuh Puluh Djaya on a Desiccated Coconut Plant, 1981; DAI (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Toward an Improved PDP Information System, 1982; Michael Morfit, Mastuhu, Donald Mickelwait, Robinson Tarigan, Jerry VanSant (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A Study of Selected Agricultural Processing Opportunities in Lombok, Indonesia, 1982; Willem G. Heyneker and Gary D. Kilmer (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Evaluation of Mae Chaem Watershed Development Project, 1983; Alan D. Roth, Lynn Hewitt, Michael Carroll, Kasem Chunko (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Upgrading the Badan Kredit Kecamatan Management Information System: Final Report, 1983; Abdulrachman Affandi and Jay Rosengard (Box 1, Folder 13)
- An Evaluation Plan for the Small and Medium Enterprise Development Project (#492-0359), 1984; Susan Goldmark (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Upgrading and Computerizing the Management Information System at Bappenas' Bureau of Foreign Economic Cooperation: Feasibility Study, 1984; Jay K. Rosengard (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Report of Survey of the Nutmeg Industry in Indonesia, 1984; James L. Woodcock (Box 1, Folder 16)
- "Analysis of External Resource Utilization for the Bureau of Foreign Economic Cooperation, Bappenas" End of Phase I, 1984; Jay Rosengard and Frank Welsh (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Management and Organization of the Information Center Office of Educational Research and Development of Education and Culture, 1984; Jerry VanSant (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Study on the Restructuring and Modernization of Smallholder Agriculture in Malaysia, 1985; Robert D. Campbell, William D. Sorenson, Chew Siew Tuan, Wong Chee Yoong (Box 2, Folder 3)
- An Institutional Assessment of USAID Program to The Indonesia National Planning Program: 1980-1984, 1985; Jerry VanSant, Benson Hausman and Sri Pamoedjo Rahardjo (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Upgrading the Bank Rakyat Indonesia DESA Management Information System: Phase I Final Report, 1985; Jay Rosengard (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Analysis of External Resource Utilization for the Bureau of Foreign Economic Cooperation, Bappenas: End of Phase II Progress Report, 1985; Jay Rosengard and Frank Welsh (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Analysis of External Resource Utilization for the Bureau of Foreign Economic Cooperation, Buppenas: Phase III Status Report, 1985; Jerry VanSant (Box 2, Folder 7)
- FID Pre-Implementation Monitoring and Evaluation Design, 1975; Jay K. Rosengard and Geoffrey D. Peters (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Institutional Mechanisms to Raise Funds for Indonesian Private Voluntary Organizations, 1986; Russell Betts (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Provincial Small Business Management Training in Indonesia: the IPPM/PPK Program, 1986; Russell Betts (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Private Sector in Development Program (in Thailand) Evaluation Scope of Work, 1986; Alan Roth (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Local Resource Management Project External Evaluation: February 9 - March 13, 1987, Joseph M. Alabanza, Benjamin V. Cariño, Soledad A. Hernando, Thomas Rose, Jerry VanSant (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Evaluation of the Comprehensive Health Improvement Program - Province Specific, 1987; Robert Pratt (Box 2, Folder 13)
- A Strategic Assessment of NGO Development in Indonesia, 1987; Russell Betts (Box 2, Folder 14)
- A Mid-Term Evaluation of the Computing Development Project BUR/83/004, 1987; Miles F. Toder, George Sadowsky, U Thein Myint (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Credit in Support of Rural Development: An Evaluation of the Credit Component of the Indonesian Provincial Area Development Program, 1988; John Dukesbury and Christopher James (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Developing Small Business in Indonesia: Reflections on the Central Java Enterprise Development Project, 1988; Boomgard, James J. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- A.I.D. Microenterprise Stock-Taking: The Financial Institutions Development. Puskowanjati Women's Cooperative, Maha Bhoga, and Yayasen DianDesa Projects - Indonesia, 1989; C. Stark Biddle, Sanjay Sinha, Michael Farbman, Don Sillers (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Impact Evaluation Guidelines for the Ministry of Agriculture, Malaysia, with addendum of October 1989, DAI (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Medium Scale Irrigation Systems in Northeast Thailand: Future Directions, 1989; Sam H. Johnson III, Sanguan Patamatamkul, Adul Apinantara, Terd Charoenwatana, Kanda Paranakian, Peter Reiss (ISPNA) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- PVO Co-Financing III in Indonesia: Program Design, 1989; Stark Biddle and Jerry VanSant (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Indonesia - Secondary Food Crops Project - Credit - Summary (Box 2, Folder 22)
- III B. In the National Irrigation Administration (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Joint Evaluation Mission (JEM) of the Government of the Philippines/FAO/UNDP of PHI/83/009 Establishment of the Animal Products and By-Products Training Center (APBPTC/Center) (Box 2, Folder 24)